MICHAEL BORADO

Full Stack Developer

© 6742 San Diego Dr. Buena Park, CA 90620

SUMMARY

Over 3 years of work experience developing a wide array of websites and applications. I have a passion for front end web development with an eye for excellent user interface and experience. I strive to continuously improve my skillset to keep up-to-date with the latest trends and technologies to provide the highest quality of code.

EDUCATION

California State Polytechnic University, Pomona

December 2015

Bachelor of Science - Computer Engineering

SKILLS

	Back End
- SASS	- PHP
- Bootstrap	- Coldfusion
- Foundation	- MySQL
- Gulp	- Node
- SEO	- NPM
- Wordpress	- Next.js
	BootstrapFoundationGulpSEO

EXPERIENCE

02/2019 - Current

Full Stack Developer

Freshnlean, California

- Developed redesign of custom shopping cart to improve conversion rate
- Contributed to the design, functionality, and experience of admin portal
- Improved desktop website page speed by 40%
- Collaborated with Designer to improve website UI/UX
- Created responsive web pages based on photoshop and sketch designs
- Met with stakeholders clarify project scope and reduce impediments
- Fostered learning culture to improve dev team programming skillset
- Introduced a build process and git workflow

05/2016 - 02/2019

Developer

Icon Internet Media, California

- Created shopping cart used on ecommerce websites
- Developed front end of tire search application using Vue.js
- Built widget in React that displays a configurable vehicle
- Maintained AngularJS application that applies wheels on vehicles
- Managed website implementation for over 25 client websites
- Designed a front end template architecture to improve project completion time
- Refactored codebase into reusable and composable components
- Ensured cross browser support for websites and applications

PROJECTS

01/2019 - Current

Custom online store

- Exploring new technologies by building a store with Next.js and GraphQL
- Created API to add, delete, and modify an item from inventory
- Design pages utilizing styled components